

Jorge Luis De Los Santos Reyes

Profile

I am a professional on the IT field, able to adapt to different environments and work under pressure. Love working as a team in a way to achieve the goals of the company, always following the strategies and guidelines provided by the organization. During my professional career I have been able to develop mostly in the QA field where I have gone from some basic manual testing to some advanced automated testing. I have over 5 years of experience in software quality assurance.

Employment History

Customer Service Representative, ACS Xerox, Santo Domingo

APRIL 2013 - APRIL 2015

- Brought forth a self-motivated attitude.
- Helped to achieve increases in sales.
- Communicated effectively with colleagues and superiors.
- Attended workshops and conferences centered around increasing customer service skills.
- Accurately verified information and updated information databases as necessary.

Food Service Lead, Six Flags Great America, Waukegan

MAY 2015 - AUGUST 2015

- Placed orders for necessary goods such as food, kitchen tools, and cleaning products.
- Assisted with food preparations prior to service.
- Handled food with sanitation and safety in mind.
- Aimed to keep food waste to a minimum by using proper food storage and recycling techniques.

Application Tech Support, Kore Wireless, Santo Domingo

DECEMBER 2015 - JANUARY 2017

- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.
- Identified hardware and software solutions.
- Troubleshooted technical issues.
- Diagnosed and repaired faults.

Software Quality Assurance Analyst, Kore Wireless, Santo Domingo

JANUARY 2017 - JULY 2019

- Test Driven Development and regression testing
- Affirmed that software functions according to functional and user requirements
- Improved and extended test frameworks and automated test sets
- Reported all defects in Jira
- Prepared, maintained and executed system test plans.

Software Quality Assurance Engineer, FlashParking, Santo Domingo

JULY 2019 - OCTOBER 2021

Details

Calle D, No. 1. Villa Carmen Santo Domingo Este, 11802 Dominican Republic 8292939998 jorge20080@hotmail.com

Skills

SOL

Git

HTML & CSS

Java

c#

Selenium

Nunit

Xunit

JavaScript

Languages

Spanish

English

Hobbies

Playing pool (Billiards)
Watching and playing baseball
Listening to music

- Performed routine inspections of finished products to check for defects and other problems before these products are shipped for distribution.
- Tracked, documented, and reported quality levels and perform analysis for quality improvement initiatives.
- Monitored risk-management procedures, and maintained and analyzed problem logs to identify and reported recurring issues to management and product development
- Coordinated investigation of quality issues with customers and suppliers.
- Wrote clean, high-quality scripts that test product functionality automatically.
- Conducted various tests for systems, networks, applications, databases, software.
- Logged and documented errors in the tracking system.
- Developed the best automation solutions based on the clients' requirements.

QA Engineer, Authority Partners, Santo Domingo

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Tracked, documented, and reported quality levels and perform analysis for quality improvement initiatives.
- Monitored risk-management procedures, and maintained and analyzed problem logs to identify and reported recurring issues to management and product development
- Coordinated investigation of quality issues with customers and suppliers.

Education

Networking Technologist, ITLA, Santo Domingo

OCTOBER 2012 - AUGUST 2014

System Engineering, UNICDA, Santo Domingo

OCTOBER 2014 - JANUARY 2021

Web Development and Internet Applications Diploma, St. Clair College, Windsor, ON

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Courses

English Course, APEC

2007 - 2009

English as a second language, ITLA

2010 - 2011

Software testing certified course, XAUREO

SEPTEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

References

Ruddy CastrofromKore Wireless

ruddy_castro025@hotmail.com | 8296651924

Miguel Angel ArzenofromFLASH

miguelarzeno@gmail.com | 8099056385

Moises FernandezfromKore Wireless

mfernandez_marte@hotmail.com | 6786835646